Eugenics Record Office Records 1670-1964 Mss.Ms.Coll.77
American Philosophical Society
- Series XII. Midget Schedules, 1840s-1964 (Box Series XII: 1-2)
  - Prohaska, Emil, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Quigley, J., 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
    Folder read "Quigley, Mrs. Jennie"
  - Raab, Meinhardt F., 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Raia, M., 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Reichert, Gilbert, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
    Coney Island Giant
  - Rice, Herbert, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Roger, C.D., 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Rogers, Sybella, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Rogers, Thomas, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Rosen, J., 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Rothchild, Florence, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Ruediger, Albert, Jr., 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Runge, Otto, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Schmidt, Joe, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Schultz, Anita, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Schultz, Dorothy, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Schultz, Elsie, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Schultz, Raymond H., 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Short, Joe, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Silvern, Charles, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Spangler, Elmer, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Spema, Pete, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Stoeffler, A.R., 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
    Folder read "Stoeffler, Amelia"
  - Sutton, Anne, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Swift, Vance, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Thompson, Buddy, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Vandola, Tony, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Victor, Joe, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Wesener, Willie, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Willer, David, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Williams, Grace Gould, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Williams, H., 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Williams, Sadie, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Wojnarski, Charles, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Wojnarski, Helen, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Wynas, Andrew, 1934 (Box Series XII-1)
  - Card File, 1840s-1920s (Box Series XII-2)
- Series XIII. Index Card Boxes, 1910s-1930s (Box Series XIII: 1-247)
  Cards that are filed by trait number (from The Trait Book), then by surname, and then by geographical locality. There are references on each card that consist of an alpha-numeric family code (e.g., Hea-26 for Heard) that can be looked up in Series IV to find the name and address of the family who submitted a Record of Family Traits schedule to the Eugenics Record Office. This series contains 247 card file boxes. (See series description.)
- Microfilm
  - Microfilm Reels (Box Microfilm: 1-70)
    General note
    The following is a list of the 518 microfilm reels contained in this collection. For a more detailed description of each reel, see Appendix C.
    - Index 1, 1683047 (Box Microfilm-1)
    - Index 1, 1683048 (Box Microfilm-1)
    - Index 1, 1683266 (Box Microfilm-1)
    - Index 1, 1683267 (Box Microfilm-1)
    - Index 1, 1683268 (Box Microfilm-1)
    - Index 1, 1683269 (Box Microfilm-1)
    - Index 1, 1683270 (Box Microfilm-1)
    - Index 1, 1683271 (Box Microfilm-1)
    - Index 1, 1683272 (Box Microfilm-1)
    - Index 1, 1683273 (Box Microfilm-1)
    - Index 1, 1683274 (Box Microfilm-2)
    - Index 1, 1683275 (Box Microfilm-2)
    - Index 1, 1683276 (Box Microfilm-2)
    - Index 1, 1683277 (Box Microfilm-2)
    - Index 1, 1683278 (Box Microfilm-2)
    - Index 1, 1683352 (Box Microfilm-2)
    - Index 1, 1683353 (Box Microfilm-2)
    - Index 1, 1683354 (Box Microfilm-2)
    - Index 1, 1683355 (Box Microfilm-2)
    - Index 1, 1683356 (Box Microfilm-2)
    - Index 1, 1683357 (Box Microfilm-3)
    - Index 1, 1683358 (Box Microfilm-3)
    - Index 1, 1683359 (Box Microfilm-3)
    - Index 1, 1683360 (Box Microfilm-3)
    - Index 3, 1683445 (Box Microfilm-3)
    - Index 3, 1683446 (Box Microfilm-3)
    - Index 3, 1683447 (Box Microfilm-3)
    - Index 3, 1683448 (Box Microfilm-3)
    - Index 3, 1683449 (Box Microfilm-3)
    - Index 3, 1683450 (Box Microfilm-3)
    - Index 3, 1683451 (Box Microfilm-4)
    - Index 3, 1683452 (Box Microfilm-4)
    - Index 1, 1683485 (Box Microfilm-4)
    - Index 1, 1683486 (Box Microfilm-4)
    - Index 1, 1683487 (Box Microfilm-4)
    - Index 1, 1683488 (Box Microfilm-4)
    - Index 1, 1683489 (Box Microfilm-4)
    - Index 1, 1683490 (Box Microfilm-4)
    - Index 1, 1683491 (Box Microfilm-4)
    - Index 1, 1683492 (Box Microfilm-4)
    - Index 1, 1683493 (Box Microfilm-5)
    - Index 1, 1683494 (Box Microfilm-5)
    - Index 3, 1683541 (Box Microfilm-5)
    - Index 3, 1683542 (Box Microfilm-5)
    - Index 3, 1683543 (Box Microfilm-5)
    - Index 3, 1683544 (Box Microfilm-5)
    - Index 3, 1683545 (Box Microfilm-5)
    - Index 3, 1683546 (Box Microfilm-5)
    - Index 1, 1683554 (Box Microfilm-5)
    - Index 1, 1683555 (Box Microfilm-5)
    - Index 1, 1683556 (Box Microfilm-6)
    - Index 1, 1683557 (Box Microfilm-6)
    - Index 1, 1683558 (Box Microfilm-6)
    - Index 1, 1683559 (Box Microfilm-6)
    - Index 1, 1683560 (Box Microfilm-6)
    - Index 1, 1683561 (Box Microfilm-6)
    - Index 1, 1683562 (Box Microfilm-6)
    - Index 3, 1683635 (Box Microfilm-6)
    - Index 3, 1683636 (Box Microfilm-6)
    - Index 3, 1683637 (Box Microfilm-6)
    - Index 3, 1683638 (Box Microfilm-7)
    - Index 1, 1683650 (Box Microfilm-7)
    - Index 1, 1683651 (Box Microfilm-7)
    - Index 1, 1683652 (Box Microfilm-7)
    - Index 1, 1683653 (Box Microfilm-7)
    - Index 1, 1683654 (Box Microfilm-7)
    - Index 3, 1683706 (Box Microfilm-7)
    - Index 3, 1683707 (Box Microfilm-7)
    - Index 3, 1683708 (Box Microfilm-7)
    - Index 3, 1683709 (Box Microfilm-7)
    - Index 1, 1683711 (Box Microfilm-8)
    - Index 1, 1683712 (Box Microfilm-8)
    - Index 1, 1683713 (Box Microfilm-8)
    - Index 1, 1683714 (Box Microfilm-8)
    - Index 1, 1683715 (Box Microfilm-8)
    - Index 1, 1683716 (Box Microfilm-8)
    - Index 1, 1683717 (Box Microfilm-8)
    - Index 1, 1683836 (Box Microfilm-8)
    - Index 1, 1683837 (Box Microfilm-8)
    - Index 1, 1683838 (Box Microfilm-8)
    - Index 1, 1683839 (Box Microfilm-9)
    - Index 1, 1683840 (Box Microfilm-9)
    - Index 1, 1683841 (Box Microfilm-9)
    - Index 1, 1683842 (Box Microfilm-9)
    - Index 1, 1683843 (Box Microfilm-9)
    - Index 1, 1683844 (Box Microfilm-9)
    - Index 1, 1683845 (Box Microfilm-9)
    - Index 1, 1683846 (Box Microfilm-9)
    - Index 1, 1683878 (Box Microfilm-9)
    - Index 1, 1683879 (Box Microfilm-9)
    - Index 1, 1683880 (Box Microfilm-10)
    - Index 3, 1683894 (Box Microfilm-10)
    - Index 3, 1683895 (Box Microfilm-10)
    - Index 3, 1683896 (Box Microfilm-10)
    - Index 3, 1683897 (Box Microfilm-10)
    - Index 3, 1683898 (Box Microfilm-10)
    - Index 3, 1683899 (Box Microfilm-10)
    - Index 3, 1683900 (Box Microfilm-10)
    - Index 3, 1683901 (Box Microfilm-10)
    - Index 3, 1683902 (Box Microfilm-10)
    - Index 1, 1684023 (Box Microfilm-11)
    - Index 1, 1684024 (Box Microfilm-11)
    - Index 1, 1684025 (Box Microfilm-11)
    - Index 1, 1684026 (Box Microfilm-11)
    - Index 1, 1684027 (Box Microfilm-11)
    - Index 1, 1684028 (Box Microfilm-11)
    - Index 1, 1684029 (Box Microfilm-11)
    - Index 1, 1684030 (Box Microfilm-11)
    - Index 1, 1684031 (Box Microfilm-11)
    - Index 1, 1684032 (Box Microfilm-11)
    - Index 1, 1684033 (Box Microfilm-12)
    - Index 3, 1684047 (Box Microfilm-12)
    - Index 3, 1684048 (Box Microfilm-12)
    - Index 3, 1684049 (Box Microfilm-12)
    - Index 3, 1684050 (Box Microfilm-12)
    - Index 3, 1684051 (Box Microfilm-12)
    - Index 3, 1684052 (Box Microfilm-12)
    - Index 1, 1684082 (Box Microfilm-12)
    - Index 1, 1684083 (Box Microfilm-12)
    - Index 1, 1684084 (Box Microfilm-12)
    - Index 1, 1684085 (Box Microfilm-13)
    - Index 1, 1684086 (Box Microfilm-13)
    - Index 1, 1684087 (Box Microfilm-13)
    - Index 1, 1684088 (Box Microfilm-13)
    - Index 1, 1684089 (Box Microfilm-13)
    - Index 1, 1684090 (Box Microfilm-13)
    - Index 1, 1684091 (Box Microfilm-13)
    - Index 1, 1711418 (Box Microfilm-13)
    - Index 1, 1711419 (Box Microfilm-13)
    - Index 1, 1711420 (Box Microfilm-13)
    - Index 1, 1711421 (Box Microfilm-14)
    - Index 1, 1711422 (Box Microfilm-14)
    - Index 1, 1711423 (Box Microfilm-14)
    - Index 3, 1711515 (Box Microfilm-14)
    - Index 3, 1711516 (Box Microfilm-14)
    - Index 3, 1711517 (Box Microfilm-14)
    - Index 3, 1711518 (Box Microfilm-14)
    - Index 3, 1711519 (Box Microfilm-14)
    - Index 3, 1711520 (Box Microfilm-14)
    - Index 3, 1711521 (Box Microfilm-14)
    - Index 3, 1711522 (Box Microfilm-15)
    - Index to Record of Family Traits, 1711553 (Box Microfilm-15)
    - Index to Record of Family Traits, 1711554 (Box Microfilm-15)
    - Index to Record of Family Traits, 1711555 (Box Microfilm-15)
    - Index to Record of Family Traits, 1711556 (Box Microfilm-15)
    - Index to Record of Family Traits, 1711557 (Box Microfilm-15)
    - Index to Record of Family Traits, 1711558 (Box Microfilm-15)
    - Index to Record of Family Traits (item 1); Special Studies ("W") (item 2), 1711742 (Box Microfilm-15)
    - Special Studies ("W"), 1711743 (Box Microfilm-15)
    - Special Studies ("W"), 1711744 (Box Microfilm-15)
    - Special Studies ("W"), 1711745 (Box Microfilm-15)
    - Index 4, 1712058 (Box Microfilm-16)
    - Index 4, 1712059 (Box Microfilm-16)
    - Index 4, 1712060 (Box Microfilm-16)
    - Index 4, 1712061 (Box Microfilm-16)
    - Index 4, 1712062 (Box Microfilm-16)
    - Index 4, 1712063 (Box Microfilm-16)
    - Index 4, 1712222 (Box Microfilm-16)
    - Index 4, 1712223 (Box Microfilm-16)
    - Index 4, 1712224 (Box Microfilm-16)
    - Index 4, 1712225 (Box Microfilm-16)
    - Index 4, 1712226 (Box Microfilm-17)
    - Index 4, 1712320 (Box Microfilm-17)
    - Index 4, 1712321 (Box Microfilm-17)
    - Index 4, 1712322 (Box Microfilm-17)
    - Index 4, 1712323 (Box Microfilm-17)
    - Index 4, 1712324 (Box Microfilm-17)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1749616 (Box Microfilm-17)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1749617 (Box Microfilm-17)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1749618 (Box Microfilm-17)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1749619 (Box Microfilm-18)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1749908 (Box Microfilm-18)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1749909 (Box Microfilm-18)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1749910 (Box Microfilm-18)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1749911 (Box Microfilm-18)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1749912 (Box Microfilm-18)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1749913 (Box Microfilm-19)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1749914 (Box Microfilm-19)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1749915 (Box Microfilm-19)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1752823 (Box Microfilm-19)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1752824 (Box Microfilm-19)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1752825 (Box Microfilm-19)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1752826 (Box Microfilm-20)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753068 (Box Microfilm-20)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753069 (Box Microfilm-20)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753070 (Box Microfilm-20)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753071 (Box Microfilm-20)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753072 (Box Microfilm-20)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753073 (Box Microfilm-21)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753074 (Box Microfilm-21)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753075 (Box Microfilm-21)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753076 (Box Microfilm-21)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753077 (Box Microfilm-21)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753078 (Box Microfilm-21)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753079 (Box Microfilm-22)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753080 (Box Microfilm-22)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753081 (Box Microfilm-22)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753089 (Box Microfilm-22)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753090 (Box Microfilm-22)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753091 (Box Microfilm-22)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753092 (Box Microfilm-23)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753093 (Box Microfilm-23)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753094 (Box Microfilm-23)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753095 (Box Microfilm-23)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753096 (Box Microfilm-23)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753097 (Box Microfilm-23)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753098 (Box Microfilm-24)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753099 (Box Microfilm-24)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753100 (Box Microfilm-24)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753101 (Box Microfilm-24)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753102 (Box Microfilm-24)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753103 (Box Microfilm-24)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753104 (Box Microfilm-25)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753327 (Box Microfilm-25)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753328 (Box Microfilm-25)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753329 (Box Microfilm-25)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753330 (Box Microfilm-25)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753331 (Box Microfilm-25)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753332 (Box Microfilm-26)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753333 (Box Microfilm-26)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753334 (Box Microfilm-26)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753335 (Box Microfilm-26)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753336 (Box Microfilm-26)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753337 (Box Microfilm-26)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753338 (Box Microfilm-27)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753500 (Box Microfilm-27)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753501 (Box Microfilm-27)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753666 (Box Microfilm-27)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1753667 (Box Microfilm-27)
    - Index 4, 1753703 (Box Microfilm-27)
    - Index 4, 1753704 (Box Microfilm-27)
    - Index 4, 1753705 (Box Microfilm-28)
    - Index 4, 1753706 (Box Microfilm-28)
    - Index 4, 1753707 (Box Microfilm-28)
    - Index 4, 1753708 (Box Microfilm-28)
    - Index 4, 1753709 (Box Microfilm-28)
    - Index 4, 1753710 (Box Microfilm-28)
    - Index 4, 1753711 (Box Microfilm-28)
    - Index 4, 1753712 (Box Microfilm-28)
    - Index 4, 1753713 (Box Microfilm-28)
    - Index 4, 1753734 (Box Microfilm-28)
    - Index 4, 1753756 (Box Microfilm-29)
    - Index 4, 1753757 (Box Microfilm-29)
    - Index 4, 1753758 (Box Microfilm-29)
    - Index 4, 1753759 (Box Microfilm-29)
    - Index 4, 1753760 (Box Microfilm-29)
    - Index 4, 1753761 (Box Microfilm-29)
    - Index 4, 1753870 (Box Microfilm-29)
    - Index 4, 1753871 (Box Microfilm-29)
    - Index 4, 1753872 (Box Microfilm-29)
    - Index 4, 1753873 (Box Microfilm-29)
    - Index 4, 1753875 (Box Microfilm-30)
    - Index 4, 1753876 (Box Microfilm-30)
    - Index 4, 1753877 (Box Microfilm-30)
    - Index 4, 1753878 (Box Microfilm-30)
    - Index 4, 1753879 (Box Microfilm-30)
    - Index 4, 1753880 (Box Microfilm-30)
    - Index 4, 1753881 (Box Microfilm-30)
    - Index 4, 1753926 (Box Microfilm-30)
    - Index 4, 1753927 (Box Microfilm-30)
    - Index 4, 1753928 (Box Microfilm-30)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763181 (Box Microfilm-31)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763182 (Box Microfilm-31)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763183 (Box Microfilm-31)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763184 (Box Microfilm-31)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763185 (Box Microfilm-31)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763186 (Box Microfilm-31)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763187 (Box Microfilm-32)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763380 (Box Microfilm-32)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763381 (Box Microfilm-32)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763382 (Box Microfilm-32)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763383 (Box Microfilm-32)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763384 (Box Microfilm-32)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763385 (Box Microfilm-33)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763386 (Box Microfilm-33)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763387 (Box Microfilm-33)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763388 (Box Microfilm-33)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763459 (Box Microfilm-33)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763460 (Box Microfilm-33)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763461 (Box Microfilm-34)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763462 (Box Microfilm-34)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763463 (Box Microfilm-34)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763464 (Box Microfilm-34)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763465 (Box Microfilm-34)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763466 (Box Microfilm-34)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763467 (Box Microfilm-35)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763468 (Box Microfilm-35)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763469 (Box Microfilm-35)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763470 (Box Microfilm-35)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763696 (Box Microfilm-35)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763697 (Box Microfilm-35)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763698 (Box Microfilm-36)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763699 (Box Microfilm-36)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763700 (Box Microfilm-36)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763701 (Box Microfilm-36)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763702 (Box Microfilm-36)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763703 (Box Microfilm-36)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763704 (Box Microfilm-37)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763705 (Box Microfilm-37)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763706 (Box Microfilm-37)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763707 (Box Microfilm-37)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763779 (Box Microfilm-37)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763780 (Box Microfilm-37)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763781 (Box Microfilm-38)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763782 (Box Microfilm-38)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763783 (Box Microfilm-38)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763784 (Box Microfilm-38)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763785 (Box Microfilm-38)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763786 (Box Microfilm-38)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763787 (Box Microfilm-39)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763788 (Box Microfilm-39)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763964 (Box Microfilm-39)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763965 (Box Microfilm-39)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763966 (Box Microfilm-39)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763967 (Box Microfilm-39)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763968 (Box Microfilm-40)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763969 (Box Microfilm-40)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763970 (Box Microfilm-40)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763971 (Box Microfilm-40)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1763972 (Box Microfilm-40)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764604 (Box Microfilm-40)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764605 (Box Microfilm-41)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764606 (Box Microfilm-41)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764607 (Box Microfilm-41)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764608 (Box Microfilm-41)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764609 (Box Microfilm-41)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764610 (Box Microfilm-41)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764611 (Box Microfilm-42)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764612 (Box Microfilm-42)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764613 (Box Microfilm-42)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764614 (Box Microfilm-42)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764693 (Box Microfilm-42)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764694 (Box Microfilm-42)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764695 (Box Microfilm-43)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764696 (Box Microfilm-43)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764697 (Box Microfilm-43)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764698 (Box Microfilm-43)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764699 (Box Microfilm-43)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764700 (Box Microfilm-43)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764701 (Box Microfilm-44)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764783 (Box Microfilm-44)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764784 (Box Microfilm-44)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764785 (Box Microfilm-44)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764786 (Box Microfilm-44)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764787 (Box Microfilm-44)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764788 (Box Microfilm-45)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764789 (Box Microfilm-45)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764790 (Box Microfilm-45)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764791 (Box Microfilm-45)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764927 (Box Microfilm-45)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764928 (Box Microfilm-45)
    - Record of Family Traits, 1764929 (Box Microfilm-46)
    - Record of Family Traits (item 1); Marriage Files ("M") (item 2), 1764930 (Box Microfilm-46)
    - Marriage Files ("M"), 1764931 (Box Microfilm-46)
    - Marriage Files ("M"), 1765324 (Box Microfilm-46)
    - Marriage Files ("M"), 1765325 (Box Microfilm-46)
    - Marriage Files ("M") (item 1); Detailed Studies File ("D") (item 2), 1765326 (Box Microfilm-46)
    - Detailed Studies File ("D"), 1765327 (Box Microfilm-47)
    - Detailed Studies File ("D"), 1765328 (Box Microfilm-47)
    - Detailed Studies File ("D") (item 1); Field Worker Files (item 2), 1765329 (Box Microfilm-47)
    - Index 4, 1765703 (Box Microfilm-47)
    - Index 4, 1765704 (Box Microfilm-47)
    - Index 4, 1765705 (Box Microfilm-47)
    - Index 4, 1765863 (Box Microfilm-47)
    - Index 4, 1765864 (Box Microfilm-47)
    - Index 4, 1765865 (Box Microfilm-48)
    - Index 4, 1765866 (Box Microfilm-48)
    - Index 4, 1765867 (Box Microfilm-48)
    - Index 4, 1765868 (Box Microfilm-48)
    - Index 4, 1765869 (Box Microfilm-48)
    - Index 4, 1765870 (Box Microfilm-48)
    - Index 4, 1765871 (Box Microfilm-48)
    - Index 4, 1765872 (Box Microfilm-48)
    - Index 4, 1765963 (Box Microfilm-48)
    - Index 4, 1765964 (Box Microfilm-48)
    - Index 4, 1765965 (Box Microfilm-49)
    - Index 4, 1765966 (Box Microfilm-49)
    - Index 4, 1765967 (Box Microfilm-49)
    - Index 4, 1766233 (Box Microfilm-49)
    - Index 4, 1766234 (Box Microfilm-49)
    - Index 4, 1766235 (Box Microfilm-49)
    - Index 4, 1766236 (Box Microfilm-49)
    - Index 4, 1766237 (Box Microfilm-49)
    - Index 4, 1766238 (Box Microfilm-49)
    - Index 4, 1766239 (Box Microfilm-49)
    - Index 4, 1766240 (Box Microfilm-50)
    - Index 4, 1766241 (Box Microfilm-50)
    - Index 4, 1766242 (Box Microfilm-50)
    - Index 4, 1766308 (Box Microfilm-50)
    - Index 4, 1766309 (Box Microfilm-50)
    - Index 4, 1766310 (Box Microfilm-50)
    - Index 4, 1766373 (Box Microfilm-50)
    - Index 4, 1766374 (Box Microfilm-50)
    - Index 4, 1766375 (Box Microfilm-50)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769006 (Box Microfilm-50)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769007 (Box Microfilm-51)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769008 (Box Microfilm-51)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769149 (Box Microfilm-51)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769150 (Box Microfilm-51)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769151 (Box Microfilm-51)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769424 (Box Microfilm-51)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769425 (Box Microfilm-52)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769426 (Box Microfilm-52)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769427 (Box Microfilm-52)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769581 (Box Microfilm-52)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769582 (Box Microfilm-52)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769583 (Box Microfilm-52)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769687 (Box Microfilm-53)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769689 (Box Microfilm-53)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769819 (Box Microfilm-53)
    - Field Worker Files, 1769858 (Box Microfilm-53)
    - Index 4, 1786795 (Box Microfilm-53)
    - Index 4, 1786796 (Box Microfilm-53)
    - Index 4, 1786797 (Box Microfilm-53)
    - Index 4, 1786798 (Box Microfilm-53)
    - Index 4, 1786799 (Box Microfilm-54)
    - Index 4, 1786800 (Box Microfilm-54)
    - Index 4, 1787023 (Box Microfilm-54)
    - Index 4, 1787024 (Box Microfilm-54)
    - Index 4, 1787025 (Box Microfilm-54)
    - Index 4, 1787026 (Box Microfilm-54)
    - Index 4, 1787027 (Box Microfilm-54)
    - Field Worker Files, 1787242 (Box Microfilm-54)
    - Field Worker Files, 1787243 (Box Microfilm-54)
    - Field Worker Files, 1787365 (Box Microfilm-55)
    - Field Worker Files, 1787366 (Box Microfilm-55)
    - Field Worker Files, 1788113 (Box Microfilm-55)
    - Index 4, 1818495 (Box Microfilm-55)
    - Index 4, 1818496 (Box Microfilm-55)
    - Index 4, 1818497 (Box Microfilm-55)
    - Index 4, 1818498 (Box Microfilm-55)
    - Index 4, 1818499 (Box Microfilm-55)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822181 (Box Microfilm-56)
    - Field Worker Files, 1822182 (Box Microfilm-56)